{
    "subject": "resource/Gramophone_record",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Gramophone record",
    "human_readable": "The label of a Gramophone record is 'Gramophone record'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9699025750160217,
            "question": "What is the label on a Gramophone record?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473250508308411,
            "question": "Is 'Gramophone record' a common label for music recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9312963485717773,
            "question": "Is there a specific purpose for the label 'Gramophone record'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131182432174683,
            "question": "If you saw a record with the label 'Gramophone record', what kind of object is it?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9127095937728882,
            "question": "What information would be found on a Gramophone record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8582658767700195,
            "question": "How would you describe a Gramophone record based on its label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502877950668335,
            "question": "What type of object is a Gramophone record?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8193274736404419,
            "question": "What type of media is associated with the label 'Gramophone record'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8020387291908264,
            "question": "What does the term 'Gramophone record' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7488934993743896,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name written on a Gramophone record?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of a Gramophone record is 'Gramophone record'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9003_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the term 'Gramophone record' refer to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9003_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media is associated with the label 'Gramophone record'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9003_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of object is a Gramophone record?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9003_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9003_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"The label of a Gramophone record is 'Gramophone record'\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because, according to document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9003/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt, the label of a Gramophone record is actually not specified as being called \"Gramophone record\", but rather it has a label on the center of the disc. There are no documents that mention the label's name being 'Gramophone record'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that labels are present on gramophone records, which aligns with the statement that the label of a gramophone record is 'Gramophone record'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information describes a gramophone record label as containing identifying information like the artist or album name, not simply \"Gramophone Record\".",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The label of a Gramophone record can vary depending on the specific record and its artist, such as \"Adele\" or \"The Beatles\", but not necessarily always being simply \"Gramophone record\".",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}